

CONTACT

Phone: +48 664 770 449
E-mail: d.kuriata88@gmail.com
LinkedIn: /in/dariusz-kuriata
GitHub: /dariuszkuriata

LANGUAGES

- English C2, German A1
- Java & Python for Testing
- HTML, XPath, CSS (Selectors)
- SQL

Tools

- Visual Studio Code
- · Git, GitHub, SQLite
- Selenium WebDriver
- · IntelliJ, Android Studio

SOFT SKILLS

- Scrupulousness and determination
- Analytical and critical thinking
- Conciseness in communication
- Fast learning and adapting to change
- Agile development process and SCRUM

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment processes pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).

Dariusz Kuriata

I'm in the process of making a career transition. After many years as a teacher I've decided to start learning something new. Recently I've been learning how to create websites and apps. I've finished Selenium WebDriver (Java) course as well as Sql for testers course based on Flask framework (Python). I'm also creating a responsive webpage. I've passed the ISTQB FL exam. I am determined to start a career in the IT world. I care about self-development, I am open to acquiring new skills and competences. I can start working ASAP.

COURSES AND CERTIFICATES

- ISTQB Foundation Level Certificate
- · Sql for Testers Certificate
- Selenium Essential Training Certificate
- Java and Python for testing purposes
- Teaching qualifications (nominated teacher)
- 1st degree School Tutor training course with a certificate

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Cooling Services Assistant at Czesław Biliński Refrigeration Systems Repair and Service

September 2019 - February 2021

- · Industrial controllers service
- · Refrigeration systems maintenance

English Teacher at EKOLA School Complex in Wroclaw

September 2018 - August 2019

- Preparing and conducting English lessons in a private primary school
- Promotion: nominated teacher

English Teacher at Primary and Secondary School in Malczyce

September 2013 - August 2018

- Preparing and conducting English lessons in a public primary and secondary school
- Promotion: contract teacher, Success: Head Teacher's award

English Lecturer at ATUT Education Centre in Wroclaw

November 2010 - June 2013

- Preparing and conducting English lessons in preschools
- · Success: Acquiring clients for the company due to a contract with a new preschool

EDUCATION

Master: English Philology translation studies: Corpus linguistic Philological School of Higher Education in Wroclaw

October 2009 - June 2011

Bachelor: English studies and teaching methodology
University of Wroclaw, Foreign Language Teacher Training College

October 2006 - June 2009